Inventory of the Papers of Lewis Preston Collins
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Unnumbered Files
  - Blevins v. Brown, 1930-31 (Box 16)
  - [Depositions for Blevins v. Cole], 1935 (Box 16)
  - Bolling v. King Coal Theatres, Inc., 1940-49, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Bonham v. Jones (See also Box 7), 1943 (Box 17)
  - Brewer v. Davis, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Bridges v. N. & W. Railway, 1947 (Box 17)
  - T.W. Brooks Estate, 1941 (Box 17)
  - Buck v. Testerman, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Byrdie Sanders Loan, 1925-26 (Box 17)
  - Calhoun v. Mason & Dixon Lines, 1950 (Box 17)
  - Call v. Call, 1943 (Box 17)
  - Commercial Liquidating Co., 1930 (Box 17)
  - Commercial Trust v. York, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Commonwealth v. Arlington, 1951 (Box 17)
  - E.K. Coyner: State Hospital Board, 1942-43 (Box 17)
  - Crockett v. Mason & Dixon Lines, 1949-50 (Box 17)
  - Culbert Sons v. Washington Co. Farm Bureau, 1926 (Box 17)
  - Catron v. American Railway Express, 1926 (Box 17)
  - Deeds, 1946-51 (Box 17)
  - Detroit Fidelity and Surety Co., 1925 (Box 17)
  - Bruce Dodson and Co., 1943 (Box 17)
  - Dunagan v. State Highway, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Farmer v. Mason & Dixon Lines, 1949-50 (Box 17)
  - J.K. Fisher Accounts, 1926 (Box 17)
  - Greer v. Bausher, 1949-50 (Box 17)
  - Hancock v. Smith, 1951 (Box 17)
  - R.K. Harden: Probate of Will, 1950 (Box 17)
  - Harris v. Marion Insurance Co., n.d. (Box 17)
  - Harris v. United States Fire Insurance Co., 1930 (Box 17)
  - Jesse R. Helton: LPC Committee, 1933-37 (Box 18)
  - Henegar Dooley Shoe Co. v. J.W. Roberts & Co., 1926 (Box 18)
  - Hicks v. Phillippe, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Hotel Saltville Sanitation, 1943 (Box 18)
  - Huff v. Hull, 1924-25 (Box 18)
  - Imperial Fibre Products v. Buchanan, 1925 (Box 18)
  - Daniel Isaacs: LPC Committee, 1927-41, (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Lawyers' Title Insurance Group, 1942-43 (Box 18)
  - Lee v. Rhea, 1932 (Box 18)
  - Lee, Rhea, Staley, 1932 (Box 18)
  - Kirk, 1943 (Box 18)
  - McCready v. Mutual Benefit Health, 1932-33 (Box 18)
  - Town of Marion v. Carrico Co., 1950 (Box 18)
  - Marion National Bank: General file, 1941-42 (Box 18)
  - Marion Produce v. Railway Express, 1942-43 (Box 18)
  - Marrow Adoption, 1944 (Box 18)
  - Mathieson Alkali Works: Swimming pool, 1943 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous papers relating to cases, found with non-legal papers, 1935-51 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous papers relating to cases, found loose, 1936-42 (Box 18)
  - Francis Moore: LPC Committee, 1927-35 (Box 18)
  - Morgan v. Henegar, 1913 (Box 18)
  - Mt. Marion Fashions, Inc., 1948-51 (Box 18)
  - Nickels Mfg. Co. v. Echols, 1925 (Box 18)
  - Norfolk & Western Railway: Closing agency -- Seven Mile Ford, 1949-50 (Box 18)
  - N. & W. Railway Blueprints: Seven Mile Ford, n.d. (Box 18)
  - N. & W. Railway: General file, 1938-43 (Box 18)
  - N. & W. Railway: Blankenbeckler Right of Way, 1942-43 (Box 18)
  - N. & W. Railway: Buck Right of Way, 1943 (Box 18)
  - N. & W. Railway v. Gammon, 1942-43 (Box 20)
  - N. &. W. Railway: Leedy Right of Way, 1943 (Box 20)
  - N. & W. Railway: Pickle Right of Way, 1942-43 (Box 20)
  - N. & W. Railway: Stanley Right of Way, 1942-43 (Box 20)
  - N. & W. Railway: Welch Right of Way, 1942-43 (Box 20)
  - N. & W. Railway Blueprints, 1942 (Box 20)
  - Osborne v. Bilbo, 1944 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous O-R, 1947-51 (Box 20)
  - Pennsylvania Casualty Co., 1940-43 (Box 20)
  - Piggly Wiggly Marion Co.: Livestock Subsidy, 1947-48 (Box 20)
  - Preston v. N. & W. Railway, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Pritchett v. Brinkley, 1926 (Box 20)
  - Walter H. Robertson, 1934-42 (Box 20)
  - Ross v. Cullop Transfer Co., 1925-26 (Box 20)
  - Rouse v. Todd, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Saltville (Misc.): Bond Issue, 1934-59 (Box 20)
  - Saltville Moter Co. v. Poore, 1924-26 (Box 20)
  - John Sanders Estate, 1943-44 (Box 20)
  - Sawyers v. State Highway, 1943-44 (Box 20)
  - Sechler v. Neff, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Oat Smith, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Soldiers' and Sailors' Civil Relief Act, 1943 (Box 20)
  - Sprinkle v. N. & W. Railway, 1949-51 (Box 20)
  - H.B. Staley, 1928-29 (Box 20)
  - H.B. Staley: Stock Transfer, 1942-43 (Box 20)
  - Stanton v. Rouse, 1949-51 (Box 20)
  - State Highway Acquisition 91 Smyth Co., 1952 (Box 20)
  - State Highway Department: General File, 1935-44 (Box 21)
  - State Highway v. Bonham, 1943-44 (Box 21)
  - State Highway v. Clawson, 1950 (Box 21)
  - State Highway v. Dyer, 1942 (Box 21)
  - Stevens v. Sprinkle Motor Co., 1927 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous S-W, 1945-51 (Box 21)
  - Titles of Empty Folders, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Lowry Lester Trent: LPC Committee, 1931-41, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - United Stores, Inc., 1944 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Auto Mutual Insurance Co., 1939-42 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Lunch v. Willett Bros., 1942-43 (Box 21)
  - Virginia State Bar, 1942-45 (Box 21)
  - Walker v. Cole, 1932 (Box 21)
  - Warren v. Copenhaver, 1947-48, -51 (Box 21)
  - Waugh's Department Store v. Sells, 1926 (Box 21)
  - White v. Carter, 1932 (Box 21)
  - John J. Wicker, Jr., 1933 (Box 21)
  - C.Y. Widener, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Youts v. Burkett, 1925 (Box 21)